Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - FRANCHISE WORKSHOP AT GMU H. ACKERMAN. C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU DEAN ELECTED PRESIDENT VACTE (L. BROWN) D. BROWN P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU STUDENT LISTED IN WHO'S WHO D. BROWN P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - "THE NUTCRACKER" PUPPET SHOW AT FAIRFAX HIGH D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU OFFERS NURSING CONTINUING EDUCATION PROGRAMS FOR SPRING. M. LESANE P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FUNDAMENTALS WORKSHOP AT GMU. H. ACKERMAN. C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - PLAY WRIGHT D' ANDREA JOINS GMU (ROBINSON PROF.) (Box Box 25)
  - GMU OFFERS CABLE COURSES ON NURSING MANAGEMENT M. LESANE. P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - OFFICE OF CIVIL RIGHTS TO VISIT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - CAUSES OF COLLEGE ATHLETIC PROBLEMS REVEALED IN STUDY. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU PRESS PUBLISHES "THE FIRST AMENDMENT" (Box Box 25)
  - NEW PROFESSORSHIP AT GMU (DR. DUNN). (Box Box 25)
  - FEBRUARY LITERARY EVENTS AT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU PROGRAM LURING SCIENTISTS BACK TO CLASSROOM BEGINS. (Box Box 25)
  - METRO CAMPUS TO HOST ALL - WOMEN ART SHOW. (Box Box 25)
  - SCHEV APPROVES NEW GMU NURSING DOCTORATE. (Box Box 25)
  - BLACK HISTORY MONTH AT GMU (1986). (Box Box 25)
  - REFRESHER COURSE FOR RETURNING NURSES. (Box Box 25)
  - FORENSICS ANTHROPOLOGIST TO SPEAK AT GMU (BASS). (Box Box 25)
  - "PORTRAITS OF POWERLESS" ON DISPLAY AT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU SPONSORS FOREIGN POLICY LECTURE SERIES. (Box Box 25)
  - NEW DEAN - SCHOOL OF BUSINESS NAMED (COLEMAN RAPHAEL). (Box Box 25)
  - THREE GMU ENGLISH PROFESSORS AWARDED NEW FELLOWSHIPS. (Box Box 25)
  - 1986 MARY ROBERTS RINEHART SCHOLARSHIP WINNERS. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU T0 SPONSOR LECTURE SERIES ON LEFTIST POLITICAL THOUGHT. (Box Box 25)
  - POWER OFF FOR WHOLE CAMPUS. (Box Box 25)
  - FULBRIGHT FELLOW AT GMU (SCHEKNECHT) (Box Box 25)
  - OSCAR - NOMINATED "SEEING RED" TO BE SHOWN AT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - MINING AND GEOLOGY SEMINARS AT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU SPONSORS TRIP TO EASTERN EUROPE. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU ARTIST CREATES WORK AT D.C CONVENTION CENTER. (Box Box 25)
  - WETA TO BROADCAST JOEL FOREMAN'S "THINKING IN THE 20TH CENTURY" (Box Box 25)
  - ARAB - JEWISH AWARENESS PROGRAM AT GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU HOSTS INTERPRETIVE ECONOMICS CONFERENCE. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU HOSTS SPRING FOREIGN FILM FESTIVAL. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU SCHOOL OF LAW FULLY ACCREDITED BY ABA. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU SCHEDULES VISIT AND FILM BY GRACE PALEY. (Box Box 25)
  - NUCLEAR WAR EDUCATION CONFERENCE SPONSORED BY GMU. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU LAW STUDENTS PARTICIPATE IN FREE TAX PREP PROGRAM. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU HOLDS LIBRARY SKILLS WORKSHOP. (Box Box 25)
  - SMALL BUSINESS WORKSHOP AT GMU DEVELOPMENT CENTER. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU TO HOST HIGH - TECH JOB FAIR. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU TO HOLD WORKSHOP FOR LIBRARIANS. (Box Box 25)
  - "COMMANDER ZERO "SPEAKS AT GMU (EDEN PASTORA). (Box Box 25)
  - GMU TO HOLD MINI - COURSE IN ETHNIC LITERATURE. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU LECTURE SERIES " THE WILL OF THE PEOPLE". (Box Box 25)
  - GMU PHONATHON 1986. (Box Box 25)
  - CONGRESSWOMEN PATRICIA SCHROEDER TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - AWARD WINNING AUTHOR, BANKS, PRESENTS POETRY READING AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - NO. VA. REGIONAL COLLEGE FAIR AT GMU PATRIOT CENTER. (Box Box 26)
  - LECTURE ON EAST - WEST RELATIONS AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY APPOINTS NEW LAW DEAN (HENRY G. MANNE). (Box Box 26)
  - POWER OUTAGE ON CAMPUS. (Box Box 26)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FUNDAMENTALS WORKSHOP AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - POET MICHAEL RYAN TO READ AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - RENOWNED POET TO VISIT GMU (ROBERT HASS). (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS OVERSEAS STUDY PROGRAM. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU EXTENDS DEADLINE FOR IAM PROGRAM. (Box Box 26)
  - SEMINAR ON GOVERNMENT CONTRACTS AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - BLACK STUDENT TO HOLD FASHION SHOW. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU HOLDS LECTURE ON JUDAISM. (Box Box 26)
  - SUMMER SESSION 1986. (Box Box 26)
  - AUTHOR/ EDUCATOR EBLE TO LECTURE AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL SPONSORS SEMINAR ON INTERNATIONAL LAW. (Box Box 26)
  - "PHILOSOPHICAL PRINCIPLES OF THE LEFT" LECTURE AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - MOSE PLANS RADON GAS SURVEY FOR VIRGINIA. (Box Box 26)
  - GOOD AND EVIL DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - KENNEDY'S ECONOMIC POLICY ADVISOR SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - SENATOR PRESSLER TO SPEAK AT GMU COMMENCEMENT. (Box Box 26)
  - MS CONFERENCE AT GMU METRO CAMPUS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO HOST PUBLIC AFFAIRS CAREER FAIR. (Box Box 26)
  - NATIONALLY KNOWN PHILOSOPHER TO SPEAK AT GMU (THELMA LEVINE). (Box Box 26)
  - JODY POWELL SPEAKS AT GMU'S UNIVERSITY DAY. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU DEBATE TEAM WINS CHAFFIN AWARD. (Box Box 26)
  - TAX PLANNING WORKSHOP AT GMU SMALL BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT CENTER. (Box Box 26)
  - "ART FROM OLDER HANDS" AT GMU METRO CAMPUS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO SPOTLIGHT " PRINCIPLES AND PROGRAMS OF THE RADICAL LEFT". (Box Box 26)
  - SMALL BUSINESS WORKSHOP ON BASIC MANAGEMENT AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - FIFTH ANNUAL STUDENT ART SHOW AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GEORGE MASON OPENS CENTER FOR MIDDLE EAST STUDIES. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU HOLDS INTERNATIONAL WEEK. (Box Box 26)
  - NUCLEAR WAR EDUCATION CONFERENCE SPONSORED BY GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - CONTROVERSIAL ECONOMIST TO SPEAK AT GMU (SOWELL). (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS REFRESHER COURSE FOR NURSES. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS A CHESAPEAKE BAY CRUISE. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS CABLE COURSE ON NURSING MANAGEMENT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS SUMMER RESIDENTIAL PROGRAM FOR HIGH SCHOOL SENIORS. (Box Box 26)
  - "MANAGING YOUR OWN SUCCESSFUL BUSINESS WORKSHOP. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU GAINS SIX COMMONWEALTH PROFESSORS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU HOSTS CONFERENCE ON INDOOR RADON. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU ECONOMIST HEADS VAE (PHILIPS). (Box Box 26)
  - NEW COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY AT GMU LIBRARY. (Box Box 26)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FUNDAMENTALS WORKSHOP AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - NEW DEAN JOINS GMU - CAS (WADE). (Box Box 47)
  - 1986 COMMENCEMENT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU PRESENTS CHILDREN'S PUPPET FAIR. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU SUMMER PROGRAM EXAMINES MIDDLE EAST CULTURE AND CONFLICT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU ESTABLISHES GENEALOGY AND HISTORY INSTITUTE. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU MARIONETTE EXHIBIT CELEBRATES 5OTH ANNIVERSARY OF FTP. (Box Box 26)
  - EXPERTS DISCUSS MIDDLE EAST CONFLICT AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - EXPERTS DISCUSS THE MIDDLE EAST PEACE PROCESS AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO OFFER SUMMER INSTITUTES FOR HIGH SCHOOL MATH AND PHYSICS TEACHERS. (Box Box 26)
  - GOVERNOR FILLS TIME CAPSULE AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - AWARD WINNING ROSLYN LATTO TO EXHIBIT AT GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO HOST GOLDEN ANNIVERSARY PUPPETRY FESTIVAL. (Box Box 26)
  - PATRIOT CLUB OUTDOOR MARKET. (Box Box 26)
  - FINANCING WORKSHOP AT GMU'S DEVELOPMENT CENTER. (Box Box 26)
  - MARY ROBBERTS RINEHART FUND NAMES NATIONAL AWARD WINNERS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO SPONSOR GROUNDING AND SHELDING ENGINEERING SEMINAR. (Box Box 26)
  - GEORGE MASON TO BENEFIT FROM VIENNA METRO. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO HOST SYMPOSIUM ON CONTRACTING FOR FEDERAL TRAINING DOLLARS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU HOLDS SESSION ON MINORITY BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU HOLDS TRANSPORTATION WORKSHOP. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO SPONSOR SUMMER RESIDENTIAL CAMPS AT HEMLOCK OVERLOOK. (Box Box 26)
  - POWER OUTAGE IN SELECT AREAS ON CAMPUS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU MARKETING PROFESSOR APPOINTED TO MAJOR UNITED WAY PROJECT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU RESEARCHER LOOKS AT INTERNAL CONTROL OF UNIVERSITY ATHLETIC PROGRAMS. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU SELECTS NINE 1986 PRESIDENTIAL MERIT SCHOLARS. (Box Box 26)
  - POWER'S OFF. (Box Box 26)
  - UNITED SAVINGS BANK OF VIENNA DONATES $10,000 TO GMU. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU TO SPONSOR ADULT AND PEDIATRIC NURSE PRACTITIONER REVIEW COURSES. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU NURSING PROFESSOR RECEIVES RESEARCH GRANT. (Box Box 26)
  - GMU OFFERS KAYAKING COURSE. (Box Box 27)
  - NEW GRADUATE DANCE COURSE. (Box Box 27)
  - PATRIOT CLUB OUTDOOR MARKET. (Box Box 27)
  - FRENCH - MOROCCAN ARTISTS TO EXHIBIT AT GMU FENWICK GALLERY. (Box Box 27)
  - THE FUTURE OF NURSING IN VIRGINIA DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - CAMPUS ROADS CLOSE FOR REPAIRS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE TEACHES READING, WRITING, SPEAKING AND CULTURE. (Box Box 27)
  - FIRST NATIONAL VIETNAMESE CONGRESS HELD AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU PROFESSIONAL CENTER TO HOST CONTINUING EDUCATION LOGISTICS COURSES. (Box Box 27)
  - SIX NOBEL LAUREATES DISCUSS THE FUTURE OF SCIENCE AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING ACCREDITED AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GEORGE MASON SCHOOL OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND ENGINEERING ADDS TWO PROMINENT FACULTY. (Box Box 27)
  - LIMITED ACCESS TO LIBRARY AREAS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO HOST SMALL BUSINESS WORKSHOP. (Box Box 27)
  - COHN, ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS HOLDS RETREAT. (Box Box 27)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FUNDAMENTALS WORKSHOP RESUMES AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU OFFERS FALL 1986 CABLE CURSES ON NURSING MANAGEMENT. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU OFFERS REFRESHER COURSE FOR NURSES THIS FALL. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU POSTS SUMMER DEAN'S LIST. (Box Box 27)
  - DISTINGUISHED POET WILLIAM MATTHEWS TO PRESENT POETRY. (Box Box 27)
  - GEORGE MASON METRO GALLERY PRESENTS PHOTO EXHIBIT ON CHARENDON. (Box Box 27)
  - PRESIDENTIAL ASSISTANT APPOINTED AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU NURSING CONT. ED. OFFERS COURSES IN PHARMACOLOGY, HEALTH ASSESSMENT AND I.V. THERAPY. (Box Box 27)
  - NEW MEMBER APPOINTED TO GMU BOARD OF VISITORS. (Box Box 27)
  - WORLD RENOWNED PSYCHOLOGIST JOINS GMU FACULTY. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO PRESENT AWARD - WINNING SPANISH FILM TASIO. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS TO HOST CONFERENCE ON COMMUNICATION, LANGUAGE AND GENDER ISSUES. (Box Box 27)
  - THE INSURANCE CRISIS DISCUSSED AT GMU'S SMALL BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT CENTER. (Box Box 27)
  - ARCHITECTS AS ARTISTS EXHIBIT AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - IBM EXECUTIVE JOINS GMU SCHOOL OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION. (Box Box 27)
  - PROMINENT STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT SPECIALISTS FILLS ENDOWED CHAIR AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU METRO HOSTS ORIENTAL BRUSH PAINTINGS EXHIBIT. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU'S HEP PROGRAM WINS AWARD. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU SPOTLIGHTS CAREERS FOR ALUMNI. (Box Box 27)
  - GEORGE MASON SETS NEW TOWING POLICY. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU EDUCATIONAL CENTER OFFERS PERSONALITY TESTING. (Box Box 27)
  - ACTOR F. MURRAY Abraham SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - WOUNDED MAN FOUND ON CAMPUS. (Box Box 27)
  - FRANCHISE RESOURCE ASSISTANCE AND TRAINING (FRAT) WORKSHOP. (Box Box 27)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE PHYSICIST TO SPEAK AT GMU ON FUTURE ON INTELLIGENT MACHINES. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO FACE OFF WITH SOVIETS IN SPACE DEVELOPMENT DEBATE. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS TO OFFER AMERICAN ART APPRECIATION COURSE. (Box Box 27)
  - SPACE SCIENTIST URGES NASA TO AIM FOR THE MOONS OF MARS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU HOLDS ANNUAL OPEN HOUSE. (Box Box 27)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FUNDAMENTALS AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - TAX LAW CHANGES AFFECTING SMALL BUSINESS. (Box Box 27)
  - YEAR - LONG HOME RADON SURVEY OFFERED BY GEORGE MASON GEOLOGIST. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU RECEIVES $45,000 FROM TRW. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO SHOW FILM "EMILY DICKENSON". (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO OFFER FOUR LIBRARY CONTINUING EDUCATION COURSES. (Box Box 27)
  - TOP ASTRONOMERS EXAMINE SUPERMASSIVE BLACK HOLES AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - AWARD WINNING CANADIAN WRITER TO PRESENT READING AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - ELECTRONIC ELECTION FORECASTING - GOP GAIN. (Box Box 27)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE SCIENTIST VAL FITCH TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE BIOLOGIST MARSHALL NIRENBERG TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - MINORITY BUSINESS INFORMATION SEMINAR. (Box Box 27)
  - MEETING OF EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF BOARD OF VISITORS. (Box Box 27)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE SCIENTIST TO DISCUSS FUTURE OF INFO. TECH. AND NEUROSCIENCE. (Box Box 27)
  - POTOMAC VALLEY WATERCOLORISTS TO EXHIBIT AT GMU METRO CAMPUS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU STUDENT RECEIVES ZONTA INTERNATIONAL SCHOLARSHIP. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL ALUMNI HOLD ART AUCTION. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU HOLDS LECTURE ON " THE BLACK FAMILY". (Box Box 27)
  - SURREALIST PAINTER MARGARIDA KENDALL TO EXHIBIT AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO HOST LECTURE ON HOW TO BETTER UTILIZE COMPUTERS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU TO PRESENT FILM, " ROBERT FROST". (Box Box 27)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE ROSALYN YALLOW TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - 1985 NOBEL LAUREATE TO LECTURE AT GMU. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU STUDENT RECEIVES $25,000 EXECUTIVE NURSE FELLOWSHIP. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU PSYCHOLOGICAL CLINIC OFFERS COUNSELING SERVICES. (Box Box 27)
  - CANADIAN SOCIOLOGIST FEATURED AT GMU FEMINIST ROUNDTABLE. (Box Box 27)
  - YEAR - LONG RADON SURVEY TO BEGINS NOV. 1. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU PROFESSOR WINS NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU SITE OF ELECTION NIGHT BROADCAST. (Box Box 27)
  - NOTED CANADIAN WRITER ROBERT KROETSCH TO PRESENT READING AT GMU. (Box Box 28)
  - POET GREGORY ORR READS AT GMU. (Box Box 28)
  - HUMAN RIGHTS ACTIVISTS LETELIER TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 28)
  - CAMPUS ALERT !! RAPE INCIDENT. (Box Box 28)
  - SHARE YOUR HOLIDAY CELEBRATION WITH A GMU FOREIGN STUDENT. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU TO HOST ANNUAL WINTER CRAFTS IN FESTIVAL. (Box Box 28)
  - FICTION WRITER MARY ROBINSON TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 28)
  - BLICHANAN GMU COMMENCEMENT SPEAKER FOR MAY 1987. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU'S INNOVATIVE PAGE PROGRAM WINS MAJOR EDUCATION AWARD. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU " CELEBRATES VIRGINIA" AT ANNUAL GALA. (Box Box 28)
  - LITERARY SCHOLAR JOINS GMU AS ROBINSON. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETING. (Box Box 28)
  - CHICAGO MERCANTILE EXCHANGE VP ECONOMICS ADVISORY BOARD. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU HOLDS REVIEW COURSE FOR STATE NURSING BOARDS. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS GALLERY TO SHOWCASE ART FROM NOVA - ANNANDALE. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU LAW STUDENTS RECEIVE SCHOLARSHIPS. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU RECEIVES $2.4 MILLION FOR SOFTWARE ENGINEERING CENTER. (Box Box 28)
  - AUTHOR OF BOOK ON MITCH SYNDER TO APPEAR AT GMU. (Box Box 28)
  - ERROR - CONTROL CODING COMMUNICATION AND COMPUTER SYSTEMS. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU RECEIVES DONATIONS FROM UNITED SAVINGS BANK. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU ARTS PATRON RECEIVES CASE VOLUNTEER AWARD. (Box Box 28)
  - PAYROLL OFFICE CLOSED FOR CHRISTMAS HOLIDAYS. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU SEEKS SCIENTISTS FOR TEACHING CERTIFICATE PROGRAM. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU EDUCATION PROFESSOR CONSULTS ON VIRGINIA PUBLIC INFO. BOOK ABOUT THE PRESCHOOL YEARS. (Box Box 28)
  - UNIVERSITY DRIVE TO CLOSE THURSDAY. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU TO OFFER LOGISTICS INSTRUCTION. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU REFRESHER COURSE FOR NURSES THIS SPRING. (Box Box 28)
  - GMU CENTER FOR THE PRODUCTIVE USE OF TECHNOLOGY RECEIVES CITICORP GRANT. (Box Box 28)
  - EDUCATION BOOK OFFERS INSIGHT INTO FUTURE TRENDS. (Box Box 28)
  - PULITZER PRIZE WINNING POET GWENDOLYN BROOKS COMES TO GMU LESANE C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - MARTIN LUTHER KING, Jr. BIRTHDAY OBSERVANCE HELD AT GMU LESANE C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - PSYCHOLOGICAL CLINIC HOLDS COPING WORKSHOP SERIES - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU HOLDS "CAREERS UNLIMITED 87" - LESANE. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU ART ALUMNI PRESENT SHOW AT UNIVERSITY'S FENWICK GALLERY - LESANE P.R, C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - CANADIAN POET GARY GEDDES TO PRESENT READING AT GMU - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - NATIONAL ENDOWMENT FOR THE ARTS DIRECTOR TO TEACH AT GMU - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS HOSTS SCULPTURE EXHIBIT - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - EAST AFRICAN VILLAGE ART ON DISPLAY AT GMU - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU ECONOMICS PROFESSOR FIRST TO HOLD VISITING CHAIR - ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU CELEBRATES BLACK HISTORY MONTH - LESANE / ACKERMAN P.R. / C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU TO HOST STUDENT ENGINEERING CONFERENCE - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU TO HOST PARENTS CONFERENCE ON STANDARDIZED TESTING - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU TO HOST HISTORICAL ART EXHIBIT ON VIRGINIA WOMEN - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU EXHIBITS WORKS BY MT. SAN ANGELOS ARTISTS - LESANE P.R / C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - FICTION WRITER PAUL WEST TO READ AT GMU - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - ROBB APPOINTED VISITING PROFESSOR OF GMU - ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU HOLDS TEST PREPARATION SERIES - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU CELEBRATES HOMECOMING - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU NOBEL MEETS VIRGINIA LEGISLATORS - BROWN M.A. (Box Box 29)
  - THREE GMU FACULTY RECEIVE GRANTS FROM NEH - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - MARCH LITERARY EVENTS AT GMU - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU ALUMNI ASSOC. ACCEPTS APPLICATIONS FOR SCHOLARSHIPS, AWARDS AND ASSOC. OFFICES - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU HOLDS GREAT DECISIONS SERIES - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEETS MARCH 4 - ACKERMAN M.A (Box Box 29)
  - GMU LEGACY SERIES FOCUSES ON THE CONSTITUTION - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - 2ND ANNUAL REGIONAL COLLEGE FAIR AT GMU - LESANE C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU SEEKS VOLUNTEERS FOR ANNUAL PHONATHON - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - PROBABLE PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE JOE BIDEN TO LECTURE ON FOREIGN POLICY AT GMU - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS HOSTS HI - TECH JOB FAIR - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 29)
  - OVERSEAS STUDY PROGRAMS PRESENTED THROUGH GMU - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 29)
  - GMU HOSTS GOVERNMENT CONTRACTING SEMINAR - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - NO. VA - PHOTO SHOW AT GMU METRO GALLERY. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU OFFERS ADVANCED TRAINING COURSE TO LIBRARIANS - LESANE C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU HOLDS PSYCHIATRIC NURSING COURSE - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU OFFERS SUMMER REFRESHER COURSE FOR NURSES - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - FOCUSING ON THE TRAUMATIC ORTHOPEDIC PATIENT - LESANE C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - $390,000 GRANT SUPPORT CONFLICT RESOLUTION AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - SCIENTISTS DEBATE EVOLUTION VS. CREATION ACKERMAN / MILLER P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - POWER OUTAGE ON TUESDAY FLASH MORNING ACKERMAN. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETING ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 30)
  - POET ADAM ZAGAJEWSKI TO VISIT GMU - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - CELEBRATED NOVELIST WILLIAM STYRON FEATURED IN FILM AND PERSONAL READING AT GMU - BROWN. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU DISCUSSES "THE LIVING CONSTITUTION" LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - PRESIDENT'S COUNCIL ON PHYSICAL FITNESS GALA AT GMU - BROWN C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 30)
  - FED. RESERVE SYSTEM OFFICIAL TO ADDRESS GMU ALUMNI AT NATIONAL PRESS CLUB - BROWN. (Box Box 30)
  - REGISTRATION BEGINS FOR GMU'S SUMMER SESSION. (Box Box 30)
  - NATIONALLY KNOWN EXPERT TO SPEAK ON " AIDS ON THE COLLEGE CAMPUS" - BROWN P.R. / C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU CELEBRATES INTERNATIONAL WEEK - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - ALL - WOMAN ART SHOW AT GMU METRO CAMPUS GALLERY C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU TO SPOTLIGHT STANDARDIZED TESTING AT PARENT'S CONFERENCE - BROWN C.I. P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU HOSTS ANNUAL HISTORY DAY. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU CELEBRATES ITS 15TH ANNIVERSARY - ACKERMAN P.R / M.A. (Box Box 30)
  - UNIVERSITY DAY ON TUESDAY, APRIL 7 - ACKERMAN FLASH. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU HOLDS "HANDS ACROSS MASON" LESANE C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU HOLDS BLACK GREEK "STEP SHOW" LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - TWENTY GMU STUDENTS SELECTED FOR WHO'S WHO - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU HOLDS ALUMNI AWARDS - REUNION BANQUET - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - GMU DISCUSSES "THE ADMINISTRATIVE STATE" LESANE C.I. (Box Box 30)
  - MEXICAN NOVELIST CARLOS FUENTES INAUGURATED NEW CHAIR AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 30)
  - SUMMER DAY CAMPUS AT GMU. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU PUBLIC AFFAIRS OFFERS MPA IN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU'S GLOBAL ISSUES PROGRAM FOCUSES ON LATIN AMERICA - LESANE P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - POWER OUT IN HUMANITIES MODULE, ACADEMIC III, ABD STUDENT UNION II ACKERMAN FLASH. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU HOLDS ADULT NURSE PRACTITIONER SEMINAR LESANE P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU PEDIATRIC NURSE PRACTITIONER COURSE LESANE P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - MARY ROBERTS RINEHART FUND SELECTS NATIONAL LITERARY COMPETITION WINNERS TURNER / ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - MARY ROBERTS RINEHART FUND ANNOUNCES WINNERS OF LITERARY PRIZE TURNER / ACKERMAN. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU EXHIBITS WORK OF WHITE HOUSE PHOTOGRAPHER LESANE C.I. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL GRADUATES RECEIVE SPECIAL AWARDS ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - $ MILLION CIT / GEORGE MASON PARTNERSHIP BENEFITS VIRGINIA ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - NEW GEORGE MASON PROFESSOR PROMOTES SCIENCE FOR THE LAYMAN ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU PRESIDENT VISITS SOUTHWEST ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU HOSTS GOVERNOR'S ASIAN STUDIES / LANGUAGE ACADEMY LESANE. (Box Box 31)
  - GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY NAMES GRADUATE DEAN ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - SOUTH VIRGINIA COMMUNITY COLLEGE PRESIDENT MEETS WITH NO. VA INDUSTRY ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - FORUM ON FUNDING BUSINESS FOR THE POOR AT GMU ACKERMAN C.I. P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU HOLDS SUMMER CONCERT PR / CI. (Box Box 31)
  - CENTER FOR COM UNITY EDUCATION AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - CONFERENCE RAPPAHANNOCK AND ITS WATERSHED. (Box Box 31)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS JULY 29. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU HOLDS LOGISTICS COURSE ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU WELCOMES HOME ITS OWN ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU OFFERS REFRESHER COURSE FOR RETURNING NURSES ACKERMAN C.I. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL RECEIVES MORRIS SCHOLARSHIP ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - FIRE ALARM TEST ZIEMBA F.L. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU PRESS ANNOUNCES PUBLICATION OF VIRGINIA ALTERNATIVES FOR THE 1990s ZIEMBA. (Box Box 31)
  - GMU ECONOMIST RECEIVES FREEDOME FOUNDATION AWARD ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - TIMOTHY J. MURIS APPOINTED TO FACULTY OF GMU SCHOOL OF LAW ZIEMBA P.R (Box Box 31)
  - GMU PROFESSOR DEVELOPS LEARNING TECHNIQUES FOR LAW ACHIEVER ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - STUDIO D FOUNDER SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 31)
  - 1987 STUDENT ART EXHIBIT. (Box Box 31)
  - NEW MBA PROGRAM BEGINS AT GMU. (Box Box 31)
  - AWARD WINNING GRADUATE STUDENTS PRESENT FICTION READING - BROWN C.I. (Box Box 31)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE HONORED IN LECTURES ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 31)
  - NEW JAPANESE TECHNOLOGICAL RESEARCH UNITS ESTABLISHED AT GMU. (Box Box 31)
  - REGISTRATION UNDERWAY FOR GMU EXCEL PROGRAM LESANE P.R. P.S.A. (Box Box 32)
  - SPACE REGISTRATION UNDERWAY FOR OPEN AIR MARKETS LESANE P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - FIRST HONORARY DEGREE AND MEDAL AWARDED AT GMU'S GRADUATION ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU NURSING PROFESSOR NAMED "BLACK NURSE OF THE YEAR" - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU HOLDS CARDIOVASCULAR SYMPOSIUM LESANE P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS HOLDS INFORMATIONAL MEETING ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU ACQUIRES COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ARCHIVES ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - MAY BOARD OF VISITORS MEETING OF GMU ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU GRADUATES DEAF STUDENT - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - WORLD - CLASS ATHLETE GRADUATES FROM GMU - BROWN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU STUDENT RECEIVES Truman SCHOLARSHIP ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU PROFESSORS RECEIVE STATE OUTSTANDING FACULTY AWARDS ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM CROWNED NUMBER THREE IN THE NATION TURNET / ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - THE MAKING OF AN ECONOMIST: SEVEN P.H.D. CANDIDATES TAKE NEW LOOK AT MARKETING ZIEMBA / ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - NEW INFORMATION CENTER OPENS IN FINLEY LESANE FLASH. (Box Box 32)
  - GEORGE MASON PROFESSOR'S RESEARCH COULD REVIVE THE FRIENDLY SKIES ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU SCHOOL OF NURSING RECEIVES GRANT P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - NEW FACULTY APPOINTMENT AT GMU SCHOOL OF LAW ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - PULITZER PRIZE WINNING POET AT GMU WRITERS CONFERENCE LESANE / BROWN C.I. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU HOLDS SUMMER RESIDENTIAL CAMP LESANE P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU HOSTS FACULTY ART EXHIBIT ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS AUG 25TH ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU PREPARES FOR SEVENTH ANNUAL ARTS GALA P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - RISING COSTS CREATE INCREASE IN STUDENT COPYING CHARGE ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - ADDITIONAL TRAFFIC CONGESTION LIKELY FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL ACKERMAN FLASH. (Box Box 32)